And I'm doing it for my daughter.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Just crap.
So I never looked into it, but the the
original the AI from the 60s
70s, 80s, it's called GOFAI, which is
good old-fashioned AI. That's actually
what they call it.
>> Wow.
>> And it was
had some DARPA funding and there were
some people
you know, it it
had some attention and some heat for a
while.
And now, do you know how do you know how
we talk about when we talk about stuff
we'll talk about we'll talk about it in
metaphors like it's like a car with
wheels that go like this? So not
metaphorically, actually
structurally do you know what GOFAI is?
What it actually is? It actually is,
this is not a metaphor, this is what it
is. It is the same thing as video game
AI.
GOFAI is just
a tree of possible states where it's
like if there's a patrolman and you
sneak past him, you alert him, he
changes his route.
>> Yeah.
>> If if you if he doesn't find you for 15
seconds he goes off back into his
regular patrol route. A big tree like
this. So if you're
a soldier in Metal Gear Solid, you would
have 15 different states. GOFAI, the
systems that people have put in place in
that have actually worked are like 600
different states, but nevertheless, it's
the same thing. It's programmed by a
human.
>> Uh-huh.
>> Which that's that's smart. Like it's
computers. That's interesting to me. I
like Mafia II. Like I get it that having
an enemy that reacts is like
interesting. But in the 60s and 70s
people were saying that that this is
what was going to replace humans.
>> Mhm.
Yeah. [clears throat]
>> Okay?
>> Sounds close.
>> No would state.
>> you're right there.
>> It's
>> You're right there. I mean and honestly
>> Hold on a second. No, no, no, no, look
Chris Can Go fi produce human level
artificial intelligence in a machine? Is
Go fi the primary met method? Is so
forget about computers. Is Go fi the
primary method that human brains use
>> Oh.
>> to display intelligence. AI founder
Herbert A Simon speculated in 63 that
the answers to both these questions was
yes.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Isn't that awesome?
>> Wow.
>> It's like it's it's interesting. I'm not
even click Herbert A Simon. I want to
see what he looks like. Is he a gay
Brazilian?
>> Brazilian.
>> Ah. No, he's a good guy. He's a good
guy.
>> Ben.
>> Oh, he's Jewish. Okay.
>> Oh.
>> Well, he's a good guy. Close it though.
Um
And it's I I'm not even I'm not even
saying this till I try to dunk on it or
something. It's just very interesting to
me that they basically invented
something that we all have We all play
Fortnite and we know how that works or
or uh Payday. Okay, we know how Payday
works. You trigger the safe and the cops
come out and they get you.
>> But it's not it's not thinking.
Yeah. Payday's Payday the heist game is
not analogous to how humans think.
Obviously.
To a to any to an idiot this is clearly
the the case that they're not the same
thing.
>> Why don't we have a pile of ants do it
instead?
>> You could have a you could make a
computer out of a pile of ants.
>> Mhm.
>> You could have the ants hold up You
could have them reach for sugar and if
they get the sugar that's a one. If they
don't get the sugar that's a zero. You
could make an ant computer.
>> Octopus and ants. That would be my
computer.
>> Yeah.
>> Yep. What up?
>> Wow.
>> You ever see the ants pull the wrench
through the maze?
>> Mhm.
>> Where they like get it in they have they
like this they try it like this and then
they pick it up they spin it around,
they figure they have to do it like
this.
>> Unbelievable. It's incredible.
>> It's like logical and critical thinking
as a group. It's
>> It's so good.
>> And then like octopus solving locks.
>> Very cool.
>> Like opening jars from the inside.
>> Yeah.
>> So good. Like flooding flooding labs.
>> I would like to think of octopus being a
like diabolical.
>> Yeah.
>> Like octopus like
>> They're probably gentle sea creatures.
They probably would say hi to you. I
think they wave to researchers.
>> Do they?
>> And then they wave they wave hi to
researchers, yeah.
>> Wow.
>> They figured out that this is amazing.
>> Something like that.
>> They're so smart you would you would
never eat them if you knew how smart
they were.
>> Don't eat octopus.
>> No, yeah, right. They're good guys.
>> Yeah, they're they're so funny.
>> They're with it. They're with it.
>> They're like this.
>> It's like eating a sentient animal from
Narnia.
>> They know what the deal is.
>> Yeah, they know the they know all the
deals.
>> Yeah.
>> They're like,
>> [snorts]
>> here we go.
Like [laughter] black lady in a
restaurant, they're like, here we go.
>> No, he's all the nodes on the AI chart.
>> I'm ready.
>> Like this guy's pre-diabetic, I can
tell.
>> Here we go.
>> He just looks at you. He looks
[laughter] at you once.
What you mean you ain't got no what you
charging me for lemons?
>> Here we go.
>> Octopus.
>> [clears throat]
>> Every [__] time.
>> [laughter]
>> It's you got a mic next to its mouth,
that's what you get out of it.
>> It speaks perfect English.
>> What's he saying? Funniest person?
>> Right?
>> The [__] is this guy?
>> And you got to get the information
before the bomb goes off.
So, you say, "Hey, I was beta. Give me
the information."
>> He's like, "Fuck you. I'm not going to
give you the information."
>> So, what do you do?
Do you waterboard him? Do you sleep
deprive him? Do you put [music] him in a
cold cell? Do you beat him? Do you put
cockroaches on him?
>> Do you put hummus up his ass?
>> I would go with you put hummus up hummus
up his ass. [laughter]
>> Is that your final answer, bro?
>> Yeah.
>> It's good.
>> This is crazy.
>> Got him right where I want
>> What kind of a game show is that?
>> That's the military. That's the
That's our
>> They're they're podcast tour that
they're on.
>> The military disclosure podcast tour.
This is the cool thing to What is this
to to humiliate the US military people?
>> What's that?
>> Just just like this whole
>> guy's doing?
>> Just like all of this.
>> I don't know. I think I mean if I had to
guess what this guy is doing, I think
it's to make it so that it seems that
the what the CIA does seems normal and
justified. Like he's a he's a whistle
he's nominally a whistleblower.
But the way he frames
what happened is a way where if you
heard it, you would understand that
yeah, it's probably necessary to put
hummus up a terrorist ass.
>> Oh, they'd be like, "Oh, no, don't do
that."
>> I'll tell you anything you want.
>> be like like imagine [laughter] imagine
like letting I'll tell Please don't. I
might be Oh, no, that'll be the straw
that breaks the camel's back if you put
hummus up my ass. He just puts it up
your ass and you're like
you're chewing it with your [__] cuz
you're starving.
>> [laughter]
>> You're chewing it like you're you're
like squeezing your [__] in and out
and chewing the hummus. Thank you. Like
In your head, you're like, "Thank god, I
was starving."
>> I tricked that guy into feeding me.
>> [laughter]
>> Who's the [__] [__] now?
>> That's the voice your ass makes.
>> Yeah. Hey, thanks a lot.
Don't put carrots up here either. That
would be delicious. You're eating
carrots and hummus with your [__]
backwards.
>> [laughter]
>> You're puking it up.
Oh, this is fun.
>> Oh, is that Jim?
>> The fake Jim.
>> Tell me that's Jim.
>> Yeah, he's good.
>> Where's Jimmy?
>> I'm told it's so beautiful. And having
Michelle,
you know, Camilla Cabello
was also amazing. It It was just a
brilliant evening. You know? Really
brilliant evening. Oh my gosh.
>> How's he supposed to move his face?
>> was off the hook. I mean, I can't
believe he committed to doing all that.
>> Any predictions?
>> Why does he sound so like that?
>> Well, I've never heard him sound like
that.
>> eyes are green, his eyes are brown, I
guess.
>> Unless someone banged his ass till his
eyes changed color.
>> The The conspiracy guys say that Jim
Carrey replaced Martin Scorsese as the
overlord of Hollywood.
>> You've been saying that for years.
>> Well, that's that's what I read.
But, it looks brown.
>> As my There goes my hero, ever since I
was a child.
>> [clears throat and laughter]
>> Jim Carrey
>> Smokin'.
>> Smokin'. Thanks, Charles.
>> It's really nice to meet you. Sounds
like fluffy like this.
>> Thanks, Charles. It's nice to meet you,
too.
>> Look at how he's like looking cute. Like
there's something [__] wrong.
>> It's so beautiful. I painted a beautiful
painting.
>> Oh [clears throat]
God almighty. Well, I mean, hey, I guess
he was good in his movies. What else can
you say?
>> [laughter]
>> He's good in his movies.
>> good in the number 23. That's for
[__] sure.
>> He's going out like a legend.
>> He chooses how he looks when he's
leaving. Being Shapes World?
>> No. Can you type Can you do Shapes
World? Is that on YouTube yet?
>> Probably.
Is this the Shapes You mean the Shapes
store?
>> Yeah, Shapes store. Yeah, yeah, my bad.
The Shapes store.
>> You seen this, Nick?
>> I got like eight of these little new
shapes.
>> What the [__] is this?
>> The Shapes store.
>> [music]
>> Wow.
What?
Is it AI?
>> Yeah.
>> Wild.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, that's [__]
Wild.
>> Wow.
>> Oh, [__]
Damn, shit's getting good.
>> No, they are getting good at this.
This is a lot of work around for Frazzle
Drip.
Wow.
>> How much money does [music] it take to
generate this?
>> Yeah.
>> $3.
>> That's the new thing they're trying to
put on us, that AI costs a lot of money.
>> No, it costs a lot of water.
>> Energy, yeah, it's energy and water.
>> Yeah, a lot of fresh water. Oh, yeah.
>> Well, you don't understand the AI cost
>> It's staying theatrical, man.
>> What?
>> He's calm. He's not wigging out.
Oh, there it is.
>> Hit escape. Somebody had a crazy tweet
breaking down. Oh, there it is right
there. The shape store
is
the afterlife for black people. It
represents the bacchanalian tempest of
chaos
that stirs in their hearts. It is
neither heaven nor hell, but a tense
purgatory of motion, wonder, violence,
and colors. The shape store is what they
grasp for while alive.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, man. All right. I don't want to I
can't
It's too depressing.
>> That's funny.
>> Um
the shape store, 2008 real footage.
>> [laughter]
>> Were we skipping stuff here? What's the
Jim Jantos?
>> Auto auto fecal. I like this. Just auto
auto [music] fecal therapy.
>> If you do this [music] just off, does it
mean you need your ass speed or or what
does it mean?
>> You do that again, I might whoop your
ass.
>> Yeah, yeah.
Oh, oh, my
>> Yo, you play with your again, I'm going
to have to whoop your ass.
>> [music]
>> It's a good thing you didn't do that in
the city. They'd put him in the loony
bin.
>> Holy [__]
>> Yeah, dude. It's always a Burning Man
guy.
>> Open up the asylums [music]
for us.
>> He looks cool. He's a little warrior.
He's a [__] warrior.
>> He seems like he smells good. [laughter]
>> It's the WWE.
>> Yeah, that's interesting.
>> Can we see his account? That's going to
be you soon, Chris.
Tim
>> [sighs]
>> Jantos. I'm a hot blooded erect spirit
of eternal sexual fire.
>> Should work for the WWE.
>> What is with that?
>> Jesus.
>> Passion is my birthright. My highest
desires are my God-given bullets.
>> Okay.
Oh, God.
>> This guy's good. Let's see what else.
>> Oh.
>> As he unlocks your lobotomy, what's this
dude? He's doing some ass. [laughter]
>> Unlock my lobotomy.
>> Unlock your lobotomy.
Eat your poop.
Why isn't he at least scooping the [__]
out of his ass with his own hands on
camera? Doing like putting, you know,
walking the walk.
>> I like the like the PVC pipe push-up
things.
>> Couldn't he have just done push-ups?
>> Alternative diameter, like different
diameter pipe, like just just
harebrained guy.
>> He's doing it with PVC. It's his his
wife's a pencil. That's what he said
he'd do.
He should he should be doing that with
fishing line.
>> Most of what you see on the internet,
most of what you see in media, is all
for the soulless, because they don't
know how to live. We know how to live.
They don't [__] know. That's why they
need all these explanations, these
Marshall Rosenberg telling
how to behave in a relationship
[__]
>> We don't need that [__]
>> Wow.
>> It's disgusting.
>> that's pretty pretty good.
>> We are naturally born, and we know how
to be. We know how to love.
>> [snorts]
>> This guy gives all of mankind a bad
name.
>> Yeah. Yeah, yeah. I feel Shame on every
girl who had sex with this guy at a
rave.
>> any manual how to [__] live
like [__] robots?
>> Did the music track just start?
>> to know how to behave
>> Can you escape?
>> [laughter]
>> What's that What else is on that screen?
>> Shame on any girl who's ever had sex
with that guy.
>> There's no escape for him. That's for
sure.
>> Can you imagine this guy getting [__]
blown?
>> No.
>> Incredible.
>> Yeah.
>> [music]
>> Dung.
What?
>> Wow.
>> You see that visor? Holy [__]
Holy [__]
>> That's cool.
>> Holy [__]
>> 6 weeks eating my own poop nearly every
day. Here are some keys. Here is Here
are my new glasses.
>> [laughter]
>> Holy [__] I've never seen anything like
that.
>> we'll go to the next. We'll go to the
next.
>> worth it to see those shades.
>> go back to What is he doing before he
eats the poo? Cuz it's 6 weeks ago.
>> [laughter]
>> [__] all these fake humans.
>> Just keep going down. What else? Before
the poo.
Oh, it's a new poo account?
>> This is bananas.
>> Calling everyone demons, he's eating
[__] and smearing all over himself. Are
you [__] crazy? [laughter]
He calls you a demon.